Nommel Isanar Amolat

Bacoor, Calabarzon, Philippines



nommel.isanar.lavapie.amolat@gmail.com



09064527653



linkedin.com/in/enaielei

Summary

I am an avid learner willing to take new challenges and opportunities for the betterment of my career and experiences. I have a keen eye when it comes to design and aesthetics especially that my first real job involved a lot of graphics design where my sense of taste for design and art was tested. I am also a fan of programming, more specifically, programming in Python.

Experience



Game Programmer

Time Wizard Studios

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020 (3 months)

- Created daily Marketing/Advertising Materials from some of the given materials from the client (videos and images) that are to be posted on different Discord servers.
- Designed some GUI of the game.
- Coded some functionalities and GUI for the game using Ren'Py game engine.

Shop Assistant

Menandro's Printing Station

Apr 2018 - Jul 2018 (4 months)

- Created designs and layouts for different needs and events for clients.
- Printed different documents (pdf, docx, xlxs).

Intern

Marilans Graphics and Printing

Jan 2018 - Jan 2018 (1 month)

- Created personal designs and layouts as part of the training.
- Involved in the process of making different printed materials such as class pictures, IDs (PVC), etc.
- Operate some of the available machinery to create their output products such as the heat press machine.

Education



Cavite State University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology 2018 - 2022



City of Bacoor Senior High School - San Nicholas

Technical Vocational: Information and Communications Technology 2016 - 2018

Eastern Bacoor National High School

2012 - 2016

Queens Row Elementary School

2006 - 2012

Licenses & Certifications

- Introduction to IoT Cisco
- Introduction to Cybersecurity Cisco
- Introduction to Packet Tracer Cisco Networking Academy
- Networking Essentials Cisco Networking Academy
- Certificate of Participation The Woman Rock-IT Program Cisco Networking Academy

Skills

Unity • Adobe Photoshop • HTML • Graphic Design • Programming • Game Development • English • Microsoft Office • Adobe Premiere Pro • After Effects

Honors & Awards

Certificate of Recognition

Aug 2017

For commendable performance during the First Quarter of School Year 2017-2018. (Rank 1 - 91.00%)

Certificate of Academic Excellence

Apr 2017

For earning With Honors Award, TVL - Information and Communications Technology Track, for School Year 2016-2017.

Certificate of Excellence

Apr 2017

For being the TOP 1 in his class ICT - 11B. He has demonstrated academic excellence and has performed at par in all of his subjects this fourth quarter of SY 2016-2017.

■ Certificate of Academic Excellence

Feb 2017

For his outstanding performance in Academics during this third quarter of SY 2016-2017 with an average of 93.75%.

Certificate of Excellence

Feb 2017

For being the TOP 1 in his class ICT - 11B. He has demonstrated academic excellence and has performed at par in all of his subjects this third quarter of SY 2016-2017.

Certificate of Recognition

Dec 2016

For being in the Rank 5 in TECHNICAL-VOCATIONAL TRACK this 1st semester School Year 2016-2017.

Certificate of Participation

Oct 2015

For his active involvement during the 2015 DIVISION SCHOOLS PRESS CONFERENCE (DSPC) with the them "The Role of the 21st Century Campus Journalism in Upholding Good Governance, Leadership, and Transparency" held on October 8-9, 2015 at Bacoor Elementary School, Bacoor City, Cavite.

Certificate of Recognition

Oct 2015

For winning 1st place in Pag-aanyo (Designing) Collaborative and Desktop Publishing Secondary Level Filipino during the 2015 DIVISION SCHOOLS PRESS CONFERENCE (DSPC) with the theme: "The Role of the 21st CEntury Campus Journalism in Upholding Good Governance, Leadership, and Transparency" held on October 8-9 2015 at Bacoor Elementary School, Bacoor City, Cavite.

Certificate of Recognition

Mar 2014

Best in Technology and Livelihood Education: Electricity.

Third Year

Certificate of Recognition

Mar 2014

Most Punctual.

Second Year

Certificate of Participation

Aug 2010

For his active involvement and participation which contributed for the success of the 2010 District Press Conference, held on August 18-19, 2010, at Talaba Elementary School, Bacoor, Cavite.

Certificate of Recognition

Aug 2010

For being adjudged 7th place in Sports Writing (Filipino) category during the 2010 District Schools Press Conference held at Talaba Elementary School, Bacoor, Cavite.



Certificate of Participation

Sep 2010

For active participation in the 2010 DIVISION SCHOOLS PRESS CONFERENCE Elementary Level held at Felipe Calderon Elementary School, Tanza, Cavite on September 23-25, 2010.